[{"answer": "You look them in the eye.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "You know, I'm a little nervous, so how do you do that?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, the first movie I ever saw more than once was \"High Noon.\"", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What -- what is your favorite movie, Mr. President?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Later on, did you realize that that was an anti-McCarthy movie?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Sometimes.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "And that all the townspeople run and hide, and there you are to face the enemy all by your lonesome?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Gosh, I don't know.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Who would you want to play you, Mr. President?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Too good looking.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "George Clooney?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "\"Descendants.\"", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What was the name of the movie?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "LINTON: Meryl Streep.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "And Hillary, who would you play Hillary in this movie?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "No, he invited me to play.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Is that true or was it your idea?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "He did?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "And --", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Invited you to play?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, I started -- I hadn't played in a couple of years.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "And what possessed you to do that in the middle of a presidential race?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "I don't know, you know, Donald Trump has been uncommonly nice to Hillary and me.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "And doesn't he realize how un-cool he is?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I don't know that.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Do you think Mitt Romney would have pulled the trigger if he was the president?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, I think, yes, it was somewhat risky because a lot of his African-American support in the churches are not for it.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Was it a mistake politically, you know, to come out in support of it?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Can't tell you.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "The race between Obama and Romney, how close do you think that race will be?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "LINTON: Because of the condition of the economy.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I think it will affect some people who relate well to businessmen.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "It seems to play with a certain group, but do you think that really will affect people and think that he can produce jobs that the president can't?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Well, we're going to bring in people from all over the country to talk about the American economy.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Tell us what you're planning to do this year, Mr. President?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Do you think we can, you know, fix the economy?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "But -- well, we've got to continue to accelerate the resolution of the home mortgage crisis.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "How do we fix it?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "The best way to do it is for America to join most other countries in using not just tax dollars to build roads and bridges and new water systems, and infrastructure is also a new electrical grid.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "How do we go about doing that?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are two things you have to do.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "What are we planning to do about fixing education in this country?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, I think two things happened.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Can you tell the American people why you think the economy went bad in the United States?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, they -- to some extent.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "And they repealed the oversight bills, didn't they?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I think he's doing the right thing.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "How do you feel about what he -- what he did today?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well, what I did was -- first of all, when I had my second heart incident and I had to put the stents put in, I had passed all my physicals, I was doing great, I was still building up plaque in my arteries.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "How did you get there, and how do I get there?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the president -- and, you know, Hillary as secretary of state has been very actively in this.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "What would you do in this situation, and what would you advise the president?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "I think so, now.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Is the world better without Assad?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I was, for two reasons.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "You were able to hold it together?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "As much as possible we raised her as we would have if we hadn't been in the White House.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "How did you raise a teenager in the White House?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Oh yes, we've watched it, I don't know, countless times.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "You watched \"The Princess Bride\" with Chelsea, what, every year?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Chelsea will be too young, I think, maybe not quite.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Chelsea, Hillary?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Well, they can go to our Web site, ClintonFoundation.org, or there is one of the Clinton Global Initiative, CGI.", "docId": "120603pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Mr. President, the Clinton Global Initiative, how do the viewers, you know, who are watching tonight, how do they get involved?", "qSentId": 472}]